<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gwalior</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="mon">Monuments</string>
    <string name="mus">Museums</string>
    <string name="hot">Hotels</string>
    <string name="eat">Eating Joints</string>
    <string name="pub">Pubs</string>
    <string name="rev">Review Us</string>


    <string-array name="mons">
        <item>Gwalior Fort</item>
        <item>Man Singh Palace</item>
        <item>Gujari Mahal</item>
        <item>Surya Mandir</item>
        <item>Jai Vilas Palace</item>
        <item>Sas Bahu Temple</item>
        <item>Teli ka Mandir</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mus">
        <item>Gujari Mahal</item>
        <item>Jai Vilas Palace Museum</item>
        <item>Archaeological Museum</item>
        <item>Scindia Museum</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="hot">
        <item>Hotel Sina Manor</item>
        <item>The Central Park</item>
        <item>Hotel Landmark</item>
        <item>Usha Kiran Palace</item>
        <item>Hotel Adityaz</item>
        <item>Hotel Gwalior Regency</item>
        <item>Hotel Shelter</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="eat">
        <item>Kwality Restaurant</item>
        <item>The Mansingh</item>
        <item>Alfanzo</item>
        <item>Param Food Complex</item>
        <item>Moti Mahal Deluxe</item>
        <item>Indian Coffee House</item>
        <item>Sagar Ratna</item>
        <item>The Yellow Chilli</item>
        <item>Chawla Chicken</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pub">
        <item>10 Downing Street</item>
        <item>Jiwaji Club</item>
        <item>BLU Lounge</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="mons_body">
        <item>Gwalior Fort is an 8th century hill fort and has a defensive structure and two main palaces - 
            Gujari Mahal and Man Mandir. Gujari Mahal was built for Queen Mrignayani, a lower caste queen 
            and hence the palace lies slightly far from the main Man Mandir palace built by King Mansingh Tomar. 
            It changed hands a few times over the years and has many other palaces, temples and water tanks. 
            The fort is irregular in profile due to the undulating ground below, and there are two gates. 
            A number of Buddhist, Jain and Hindu temples lie inside the fort.</item>
        <item>Man Mandir Palace lies within the Gwalior Fort and was built by Maharaja Man Singh of the Tomar dynasty.
            There has been significant damage to the palace over the centuries but some elements still remain to speak
            of the grandiose palace of yore. The palace walls have a spectacular frieze of ducks wading in the water but
            the rooms that once served as music halls or durbar halls are largely dilapidated now. An underfround dungeon
            in the palace was used by Aurangzeb to have his brother Murad incarcerated and executed. Other important parts
            of the palace include Jauhar Kund, Jhulagar, Kesar Kunda and Phansi Ghar.</item>
        <item>Gujari Mahal, Gwalior has one of the best exteriors and utmost care has been taken for its preservation.
            The palace now has an archeological museum that has a large collection of Hindu and Jain sculptures,
            archeological pieces from1st and the 2nd century B.C, copies of Bagh cave frescoes and Terracotta items.
            The statue of Salbhanjika, a marvelous piece in miniature is in the custody of the museum’s curator and can
            be seen on request. Thee is also a school within the Gujari Mahal, Madhya Pradesh premises which was meant
            for the British soldiers. Now it is run by the Scindia’s as is regarded as one of the best schools in the country.</item>
        <item>The Surya Mandir, Gwalior or the Sun Temple was constructed in 1988 by G.D Birla, the famous industrialist of India.
            It is influenced by the famous Sun Temple at Konark in Orissa. The city of Gwalior dates back to the 8th century and
            has been witness to some of the greatest Rajput clans like the Prathiharas, the Kachwahs and the Tomars. Stories go around
            that Maharaja Suraj Sen of the Kachwaha dynesty was down with a deadly disease and was cured by the hermit-saint Gwalipa.
            It was out of gratitude to him that Suraj Sen built the City of Gwalior.
            The Surya Mandir, Madhya Pradesh is one of the new entrants into the list of the places of interest in Gwalior.
            The temple is one of the architectural wonders and has a beautiful sculpture of Lord Surya in the temple premises.
            Surya Temple, Gwalior has captivating exteriors which has been built of red sand stone.The temple interior has white
            marble and this adds to the exotic beauty of this marvelous creation.</item>
        <item>The collection at Jai Vilas Palace Museum includes of largest pair of chandeliers in the world, silver carriage,
            oil painting by Raja Ravi Verma, Malabar furniture, Malabar furniture, crystal furniture, palki (Palanquin), pooja ghar,
            Jacobean furniture, Napolean table, miniature paintings, lithograph, royal old photograph, silver train, Chinese pot,
            clothes and footwear of the royalty, Jain sculpture, Lord Vishnu bronze statue, Balgopal bronze statue, weapons and more.
            One of the most opulent buildings built then, the museum showcases a collection of objects, artifacts etc belonging in the
            19th and 20th century, focusing on art and craft. The collection at the museum has been brought from all around the world.
            The palace museum also consists of swords that date back to the times of Mughal Emperors Aurangzeb and Shah Jahan. Along
            with the swords, there is the original shield of Jhansi Ki Rani, Laxmi Bai.</item>
        <item>Sas Bahu temple in Gwalior is famous temple, is dedicated to Lord Vishnu by the King Mahipala. Lord Vishnu is also
            known as Sahastrabahu,the one with many hands. But gradually the name changed into Sas Bahu Temple, perhaps by
            mispronunciation, or misinterpretation. The temple has rare quality of architectural skill displayed in it,
            it has all the qualities of a fabulous worship. There are two temples, which are conjointly known as the Sas Bahu Temple
            . One of the temples is bigger than the other, and perhaps for that reason, one is considered as the Mother-in
            Law whiles the other as the Daughter-in-Law. Graceful figures are in scripted on the wall of the temple and there are
            pillars that are also display architectural skills.</item>
        <item>Teli Ka Mandir, Madhya Pradesh is a towering structure of about 100 feet. It is has unique architectural style and
            resembles a Prathihara Vishnu temple.The shape of the roof or Shikhara can be easily discerned as Dravidian and the
            embellishments are distintively Indo Aryan. The decorations are of the Nagara Style, a well known art form of Northern
            India. The complex of Teli Ka Mandir, Gwalior is filled with figures of river goddesses, coiled serpents, amorous couples
            and a flying Garuda, the vehicle of Lord Vishnu.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="mons_tims">
        <item>Open All Week (08:00 AM - 06:00 PM)</item>
        <item>Open All Week (08:00 AM - 07:00 PM)</item>
        <item>Open All Week (08:00 AM - 07:00 PM)</item>
        <item>Open All Week (08:00 AM - 07:00 PM)</item>
        <item>Closed On Monday (10:00 AM - 05:00 PM)</item>
        <item>Open All Week (08:00 AM - 06:00 PM)</item>
        <item>Open All Week (08:00 AM - 06:00 PM)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mons_fee">
        <item>Entrance Fee \n
            Indians: Rs. 75 \n
            Others: US $ 5 or INR 250 \n \n
            Camera Fee \n
            None
        </item>
        <item>Entrance Fee \n
            Indians: Rs. 75 \n
            Others: US $ 5 or INR 250 \n \n
            Camera Fee \n
            None
        </item>
        <item>Entrance Fee \n
            Indians: Rs. 75 \n
            Others: US $ 5 or INR 250 \n \n
            Camera Fee \n
            None
        </item>
        <item>Entrance Fee \n
            Indians: Rs. 75 \n
            Others: US $ 5 or INR 250 \n \n
            Camera Fee \n
            None
        </item>
        <item>Entrance Fee \n
            Indians: Rs. 75 \n
            Others: US $ 5 or INR 250 \n \n
            Camera Fee \n
            None
        </item>
        <item>Entrance Fee \n
            Indians: Rs. 75 \n
            Others: US $ 5 or INR 250 \n \n
            Camera Fee \n
            None
        </item>
        <item>Entrance Fee \n
            Indians: Rs. 75 \n
            Others: US $ 5 or INR 250 \n \n
            Camera Fee \n
            None
        </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
